okay I've Never filmed a video this this
is the sideline clam um but we're going
to use a band so it's the band sideline
clam you are going to put your feet
through the band now I like doing it
right at knee
level
and when you lay on your side a lot of
people try to make their hips straight
go into a lot of hip flexion so try and
get around a 90° hip angle
here come down on your side now see what
I'm going to do to my feet here I'm
going to post off like that I'm not
going to go at my heels I'm actually
going to post off like this that helps
it creates a more stable base and I am
not going to lean back like this I'm
going to stay this way just come
straight
[Music]
up Swit to the other side
keep that hip
flection okay post off at the
feet works really well I like to have
people do this this or uh band seated
hip abduction every workout so they're
always doing some sort of lateral
rotational glute exercise because it's
very low stress um doesn't t the CNS um
you can get a lot of metabolic stress a
lot of burn into the glutes Without
Really compromising the next day's
workout hope you like it